Finding Aid for the University of Tennessee Theatre Collection, 1901- AR.0235
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 2-19; I; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
  - Individual Plays, 1941 February 18-2010 December 19; A; (Playbills, Photographs, Press Clippings, Production Materials, Posters, Stage Designs, and Scrapbooks)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 May 27-June 12; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 May 27-June 12; (4 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 May 27-June 12; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 May 27-June 12; (6 of 6); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - You Can't Take It With You (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 September 2-18; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - You Can't Take It With You (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 September 2-18; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - You Can't Take It With You (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 September 2-18; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - You Can't Take It With You (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 September 2-18; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - You Can't Take It With You (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 September 2-18; (5 of 5); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Cotton Patch Gospel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 October 14-29; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Cotton Patch Gospel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 October 14-29; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Cotton Patch Gospel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 October 14-29; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Cotton Patch Gospel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 October 14-29; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Cotton Patch Gospel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 October 14-29; (5 of 5); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Little Shop of Horrors (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1994 November 3-19; (1 of 5); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Little Shop of Horrors (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1994 November 3-19; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Little Shop of Horrors (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1994 November 3-19; (3 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Little Shop of Horrors (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1994 November 3-19; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Little Shop of Horrors (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1994 November 3-19; (5 of 5); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 November 25-December 21; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 November 25-December 21; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 November 25-December 21; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 November 25-December 21; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 November 25-December 21; (5 of 5); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - The Grapes of Wrath (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 February 3-18; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - The Grapes of Wrath (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 February 3-18; (2 of 4); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - The Grapes of Wrath (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 February 3-18; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - The Grapes of Wrath (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 February 3-18; (4 of 4); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Tango (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1995 March 2-12; (1 of 3); (Playbill and Flyer) (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Tango (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1995 March 2-12; (2 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Tango (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1995 March 2-12; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Dracula: Prince of the Dark (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 March 31-April 15; (1 of 6); (Playbills, Postcards, and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Dracula: Prince of the Dark (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 March 31-April 15; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Dracula: Prince of the Dark (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 March 31-April 15; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Dracula: Prince of the Dark (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 March 31-April 15; (4 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Dracula: Prince of the Dark (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 March 31-April 15; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Dracula: Prince of the Dark (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 March 31-April 15; (6 of 6); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Lettice and Lovage (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 May 5-20; (1 of 5); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Lettice and Lovage (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 May 5-20; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Lettice and Lovage (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 May 5-20; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Lettice and Lovage (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 May 5-20; (4 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Lettice and Lovage (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 May 5-20; (5 of 5); (Financial Materials) (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (1 of 11); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (2 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (3 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (4 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (5 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (6 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (7 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (8 of 11); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (9 of 11); (Negatives) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (10 of 11); (Production Materials) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The Cherry Orchard (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 September 1-16; (11 of 11); (Financial Materials/Grant Applications) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Lend Me a Tenor (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 October 13-29; (1 of 7); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Lend Me a Tenor (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 October 13-29; (2 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Lend Me a Tenor (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 October 13-29; (3 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Lend Me a Tenor (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 October 13-29; (4 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Lend Me a Tenor (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 October 13-29; (5 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Lend Me a Tenor (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 October 13-29; (6 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Lend Me a Tenor (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 October 13-29; (7 of 7); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - God's Country (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1995 November 3-11; (1 of 6); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - God's Country (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1995 November 3-11; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - God's Country (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1995 November 3-11; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - God's Country (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1995 November 3-11; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - God's Country (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1995 November 3-11; (5 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - God's Country (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1995 November 3-11; (6 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - She Loves Me (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 November 17-December 8; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - She Loves Me (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 November 17-December 8; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - She Loves Me (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 November 17-December 8; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - She Loves Me (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 November 17-December 8; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - She Loves Me (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 November 17-December 8; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - She Loves Me (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1995 November 17-December 8; (6 of 6); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - The Country Wife (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 February 23-March 9; (1 of 6); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - The Country Wife (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 February 23-March 9; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - The Country Wife (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 February 23-March 9; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - The Country Wife (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 February 23-March 9; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - The Country Wife (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 February 23-March 9; (5 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - The Country Wife (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 February 23-March 9; (6 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Three Tall Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 March 29-April 13; (1 of 6); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Three Tall Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 March 29-April 13; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Three Tall Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 March 29-April 13; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Three Tall Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 March 29-April 13; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Three Tall Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 March 29-April 13; (5 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Three Tall Women (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 March 29-April 13; (6 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - The Trial (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 April 25-May 4; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - The Trial (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 April 25-May 4; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - The Trial (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 April 25-May 4; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Trial (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 April 25-May 4; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Trial (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 April 25-May 4; (5 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - The Trial (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 April 25-May 4; (6 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - La Cage Aux Folles (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 May 30-June 15; (1 of 8); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - La Cage Aux Folles (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 May 30-June 15; (2 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - La Cage Aux Folles (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 May 30-June 15; (3 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - La Cage Aux Folles (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 May 30-June 15; (4 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - La Cage Aux Folles (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 May 30-June 15; (5 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - La Cage Aux Folles (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 May 30-June 15; (6 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - La Cage Aux Folles (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 May 30-June 15; (7 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - La Cage Aux Folles (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 May 30-June 15; (8 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Lost in Yonkers (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 August 30-September 14; (1 of 6); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Lost in Yonkers (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 August 30-September 14; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Lost in Yonkers (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 August 30-September 14; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Lost in Yonkers (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 August 30-September 14; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Lost in Yonkers (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 August 30-September 14; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Lost in Yonkers (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 august 30-September 14; (6 of 6); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Grease (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 October 11-27; (1 of 6); (Playbill and Flyers) (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Grease (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 October 11-27; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Grease (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 October 11-27; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Grease (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 October 11-27; (4 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Grease (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 October 11-27; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Grease (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 October 11-27; (6 of 6); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Orleanna (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 November 1-17; (1 of 6); (Playbills, Flyers, and Postcards) (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Orleanna (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 November 1-17; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Orleanna (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 November 1-17; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Orleanna (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 November 1-17; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Orleanna (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 November 1-17; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Orleanna (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1996 November 1-17; (6 of 6); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 November 22-December 21; (1 of 7); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 November 22-December 21; (2 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 November 22-December 21; (3 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 November 22-December 21; (4 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 November 22-December 21; (5 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 November 22-December 21; (6 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - A Christmas Carol (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1996 November 22-December 21; (7 of 7); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Candida (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 February 7-22; (1 of 9); (Playbills, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Candida (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 February 7-22; (2 of 9); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Candida (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 February 7-22; (3 of 9); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Candida (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 February 7-22; (4 of 9); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Candida (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 February 7-22; (5 of 9); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Candida (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 February 7-22; (6 of 9); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Candida (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 February 7-22; (7 of 9); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Candida (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 February 7-22; (8 of 9); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Candida (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 February 7-22; (9 of 9); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (1 of 10); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (2 of 10); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (3 of 10); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (4 of 10); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (5 of 10); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (6 of 10); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (7 of 10); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (8 of 10); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (9 of 10); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Andorra (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 March 7-22; (10 of 10); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - The Bronte Cycle (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 April 10-May 3; (1 of 8); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - The Bronte Cycle (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 April 10-May 3; (2 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - The Bronte Cycle (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 April 10-May 3; (3 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - The Bronte Cycle (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 April 10-May 3; (4 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - The Bronte Cycle (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 April 10-May 3; (5 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - The Bronte Cycle (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 April 10-May 3; (6 of 8); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - The Bronte Cycle (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 April 10-May 3; (7 of 8); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - The Bronte Cycle (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 April 10-May 3; (8 of 8); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Much Ado About Nothing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 May 30-June 15; (1 of 4); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Much Ado About Nothing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 May 30-June 15; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Much Ado About Nothing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 May 30-June 15; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Much Ado About Nothing (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 May 30-June 15; (4 of 4); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Terra Nova (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 August 29-September 13; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Terra Nova (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 August 29-September 13; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Terra Nova (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 August 29-September 13; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Terra Nova (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 August 29-September 13; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Terra Nova (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 August 29-September 13; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Terra Nova (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 August 29-September 13; (6 of 6); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Our Town (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 October 10-25; (1 of 7); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Our Town (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 October 10-25; (2 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Our Town (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 October 10-25; (3 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Our Town (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 October 10-25; (4 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Our Town (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 October 10-25; (5 of 7); (Photographs) (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Our Town (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 October 10-25; (6 of 7); (Negatives) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Our Town (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 October 10-25; (7 of 7); (Production Materials) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Mein Kampf (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 October 31-November 15; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Mein Kampf (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 October 31-November 15; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Mein Kampf (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 October 31-November 15; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Mein Kampf (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 October 31-November 15; (4 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Mein Kampf (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 October 31-November 15; (5 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Mein Kampf (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1997 October 31-November 15; (6 of 6); (Financial Materials) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - My Three Angels (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 November 21-December 11; (1 of 6); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - My Three Angels (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 November 21-December 11; (2 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - My Three Angels (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 November 21-December 11; (3 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - My Three Angels (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 November 21-December 11; (4 of 6); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - My Three Angels (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 November 21-December 11; (5 of 6); (Negatives) (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - My Three Angels (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1997 November 21-December 11; (6 of 6); (Production Materials) (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Shadow of the Vampire: The Bela Lugosi Story (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1998 January 30-February 14; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Shadow of the Vampire: The Bela Lugosi Story (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1998 January 30-February 14; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Shadow of the Vampire: The Bela Lugosi Story (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1998 January 30-February 14; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Shadow of the Vampire: The Bela Lugosi Story (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1998 January 30-February 14; (4 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Shadow of the Vampire: The Bela Lugosi Story (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1998 January 30-February 14; (5 of 5); (Production Materials) (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - The Seagull (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1998 February 27-March 13; (1 of 5); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - The Seagull (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1998 February 27-March 13; (2 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - The Seagull (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 1998 February 27-March 13; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 18, Folder 22)